What things should you keep in mind before buying a health care plan? The
most
important thing is your basic sum assured because
this sum assured is going to help you everywhere.
It is going to give you renewal benefit.
Your new claim
bonus is going to be made on the basis of this. Secondly, there should not be any kind
of room rent capping. There should
not be any kind of disease capping. Is there a
waiting period for pre-existing diseases?
Both of these should be very low, the lower the better.
No claim bonus should definitely be
included in your policy. If
you have not used the policy in any year, then
you should get nuclear bonus.
For how many days is the policy covering you for pre and post hospitalization?
Any kind of maternity
benefit in the policy. If you are newly
married, then
what is the waiting period for maternity benefit? Day care treatment should be
included in it. Advanced care
treatment should be included in it.
And if your policy claim is
over within a year, then it  A renewal
benefit should also be included. Finally,
check in which zones and in
which ways this policy is applicable to you.
For more information and
to purchase the policy, you can contact us on the given numbers
and through our website.
Thank you.